A Register of the Stephen J. Tonsor Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence, 1946-1998 and undated.
  - Porter, Frederick A., 1971 (Folder 18: 16)
  - Porter, John W., 1969 (Folder 18: 17)
  - Potter, J. C., 1971 (Folder 18: 18)
  - Powell, Ronald R., undated (Folder 18: 19)
  - Pratt, Lawrence D., 1969-1971 (Folder 18: 20)
  - Prentice, Edward A., 1970-1984 (Folder 18: 21)
  - Prentice, Paul E., 1984 (Folder 18: 22)
  - Preston, Robert A., 1973-1974 (Folder 18: 23)
  - Price, Ben S., 1985 (Folder 18: 24)
  - Price, Jacob M., 1966-1998 and undated (Folder 18: 25)
  - Proulx, Ron, 1970 (Folder 18: 26)
  - Prout, Jerry, 1975 (Folder 18: 27)
  - Provost, William, 1980 (Folder 18: 28)
  - Proxmire, William, 1971 (Folder 18: 29)
  - Pursell, Carl D., 1981-1988 (Folder 18: 30)
  - Putnam, Lloyd W., 1968 (Folder 18: 31)
  - Quennell, Peter, 1958 (Folder 18: 32)
  - Quinlivan, Gary M., 1997 (Folder 18: 33)
  - Raico, Ralph, 1965-1975 (Folder 18: 34)
  - Ralls, Walter A., 1983 (Folder 18: 35)
  - Randall, Bernice, 1968-1969 (Folder 18: 36)
  - Rarick, Margie Needham, 1972 (Folder 18: 37)
  - Rasmusson, Edith (Mrs. H. Richard), 1972 (Folder 18: 38)
  - Rausch, James S., 1976 (Folder 18: 39)
  - Read, Leonard E., 1970-1971 (Folder 18: 40)
  - Reagan-Bush, '84, 1984 (Folder 18: 41)
  - Reagan, Ronald, 1981 (Folder 18: 42)
  - Red Cross of the Democratic Republic of North Vietnam, 1969 (Folder 18: 43)
  - Reddy, William, 1986 (Folder 18: 44)
  - Reed, John Shelton, 1994 (Folder 18: 45)
  - Reed, Ted, 1986 (Folder 18: 46)
  - Regnery, Alfred S., 1996 (Folder 18: 47)
  - Regnery, Eleanor S. (Mrs. Henry Regnery), 1976-1980 and undated (Folder 18: 48)
  - Regnery, Henry.
    Also includes Henry Regnery Company, Publishers
    - undated (Folder 18: 49)
    - 1946-1959 (Folder 18: 50)
    - 1952-1968 (Folder 18: 51)
    - 1969-1971 (Folder 18: 52)
    - 1972-1973 (Box-folder 19: 1)
    - 1974-1975 (Folder 19: 2)
    - 1976 (Folder 19: 3)
    - 1977 (Folder 19: 4)
    - 1978 (Folder 19: 5)
    - 1979 (Folder 19: 6)
    - 1980-1981 (Folder 19: 7)
    - 1982 (Folder 19: 8)
    - 1983 (Folder 19: 9)
    - 1984 (Folder 19: 10)
    - 1985 (Box-folder 20: 1)
    - 1986 (Folder 20: 2)
    - 1987 (Folder 20: 3)
    - 1988 (Folder 20: 4)
    - 1989 (Folder 20: 5-6)
    - 1990 (Folder 20: 7-8)
    - 1991-1993 (Box-folder 21: 1)
    - 1994 (Folder 21: 2-3)
    - 1995 (Folder 21: 4-5)
    - 1996 (Folder 21: 6)
  - Reich, Virginia, 1975 (Folder 21: 7)
  - Reilly, Robert W., 1958 (Folder 21: 8)
  - Reinerman, Alan J., 1975-1980 (Folder 21: 9)
  - Reis Irwin H., 1965 (Folder 21: 10)
  - Remick, Carl, 1981 (Folder 21: 11)
  - Remini, Robert V., 1971 (Folder 21: 12)
  - Reuland, Daniel Scott, 1983 (Folder 21: 13)
  - Rever, Philip R., 1970-1971 (Folder 21: 14)
  - Review of Politics, 1980 (Folder 21: 15)
  - Reynolds, Richard G., 1969 (Folder 21: 16)
  - Rhinehart and Company Incorporated Publishers, 1958-1959. (Folder 21: 17)
    Includes an agreement with Stephen Tonsor, 1958 July 1
  - Rhodes, Frank H. T., 1975 (Folder 21: 18)
  - Richtmann, David P., 1971-1982 (Folder 21: 19)
  - Richtmyer, David L., 1982 (Folder 21: 20)
  - Riggs, Donald E., 1993 (Folder 21: 21)
  - Ringrose, David, 1984-1986 (Folder 21: 22)
  - Ritchie, Robert, 1964-1968 (Folder 21: 23)
  - Rivero, F., 1991 (Folder 21: 24)
  - Robbins, Caroline, 1974 (Folder 21: 25)
  - Robert Bosch Stiftung Gmbh, 1982 (Folder 21: 26)
  - Robinson, Joan, 1968 (Folder 21: 27)
  - Robinson, Paul, 1986 (Folder 21: 28)
  - Robinson, Walter B., Mrs., 1970 (Folder 21: 29)
  - Roche, George C., III, 1971-1994 (Box-folder 22: 1)
  - Roche, Lissa, 1985-1989 (Folder 22: 2)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1975 (Folder 22: 3)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1963 (Folder 22: 4)
  - Rockford Institute, 1984-1997 (Folder 22: 5)
  - Rogers, George C., Jr., 1984 (Folder 22: 6)
  - Rogge, Benjamin A., 1967-1971 (Folder 22: 7)
  - Romney, George, 1966 (Folder 22: 8)
  - Ronning, Hal, 1988 (Folder 22: 9)
  - Rooney, William J., 1971 (Folder 22: 10)
  - Roper, Coy, 1987-1988 (Folder 22: 11)
  - Ross, Mitchell S., 1986 (Folder 22: 12)
  - Ross, Stanley R., 1975-1976 (Folder 22: 13)
  - Rozek, Edward J., 1970 (Folder 22: 14)
  - Ruch, Ulrich, 1974 (Folder 22: 15)
  - Rule, Philip C., 1974 (Folder 22: 16)
  - Rundell, Walter, Jr., 1963 (Folder 22: 17)
  - Rupprecht, Nancy E., 1979-1985 and undated (Folder 22: 18)
  - Ruud, Charles A., 1970 (Folder 22: 19)
  - Ryn, Claes G., 1985-1991 (Folder 22: 20)
  - Sack, James J., 1970-1983 (Folder 22: 21)
  - Saffell, David, 1988 (Folder 22: 22)
  - Salahuddin, Mohammad, 1983-1984 (Folder 22: 23)
  - Sampson, Bob, 1984 (Folder 22: 24)
  - Sanders, Jack T., 1987 (Folder 22: 25)
  - Sandmel, Samuel, 1967 (Folder 22: 26)
  - Sandoz, Ellis, 1991 (Folder 22: 27)
  - Sanford, Donald G., 1967-1991 (Folder 22: 28)
  - Savory, Laina, 1986 (Folder 22: 29)
  - Sawyer, Ralph A., 1957 (Folder 22: 30)
  - Scarborough, William K., 1985-1986 (Folder 22: 31)
  - Schadler, Robert A., 1971-1996. (Folder 22: 32)
    See also Intercollegiate Studies Institute, Inc.
  - Scheetz, M. JoEllen, 1969-1970 (Folder 22: 33)
  - Schiller, M. Dean, 1971 (Folder 22: 34)
  - Schilling, Hayden, 1986 (Folder 22: 35)
  - Schlamm, William S., 1967 (Folder 22: 36)
  - Schlesinger, Stephen L., 1982 (Folder 22: 37)
  - Schmandt, Raymond H., 1968-1969 (Folder 22: 38)
  - Schmidt, Agatha, 1969 and undated (Folder 22: 39)
  - Schmidt, Emily, 1985-1993 and undated (Folder 22: 40)
  - Schmidt, Wilson, 1970 and undated (Folder 22: 41)
  - Scholz, Bernard W., 1993 (Folder 22: 42)
  - Schrand, Timothy, undated (Folder 22: 43)
  - Schroeder, Paul W., 1986 (Folder 22: 44)
  - Schultz, Helen E., 1969-1973 (Folder 22: 45)
  - Scobie, Ingrid W., 1971 (Folder 22: 46)
  - Scott, Foresman and Company, 1979-1985 (Folder 22: 47)
  - Segel, Edward B., 1984 (Folder 22: 48)
  - Seigel, Jerrold, 1971-1984 (Folder 22: 49)
  - Seigneuret, Jean-Charles, 1981-1985. (Folder 22: 50)
    See also Lester A. Shepard
  - Sertz(?), Karl, 1971 and undated (Folder 22: 51)
  - Shapiro, Harold T., 1982 (Folder 22: 52)
  - Sharp, Robert Brooke, 1973-1974 (Folder 22: 53)
  - Shaughnessy, Andrew, 1986 (Folder 22: 54)
  - Shepard, Lester A., 1981. (Folder 22: 55)
    See also Jean-Charles Seigneuret
  - Shields, Dennis J., 1993 (Folder 22: 56)
  - Shontz, Patricia J., 1974 (Folder 22: 57)
  - Shyrock, Richard H., 1961 (Folder 22: 58)
  - Shudy(?) Arthur, undated (Folder 22: 59)
  - Shy, John and Arlene, 1996 (Folder 22: 60)
  - Sidar, Alexander G., Jr., 1970 (Folder 22: 61)
  - Sigler, Ernest T., 1970 (Box-folder 23: 1)
  - Silva, Moises, 1974 (Folder 23: 2)
  - Silverburg, Sanford R., 1971 (Folder 23: 3)
  - Silverman, Dan P., 1986 (Folder 23: 4)
  - Silvern, G. Steven Jack, 1967 (Folder 23: 5)
  - Simms, James V. Jr., 1986 (Folder 23: 6)
  - Sirico, Robert A., 1991-1993 (Folder 23: 7)
  - Skic(?) Larry, undated (Folder 23: 8)
  - Slayton, Mary E., 1979-1983 (Folder 23: 9)
  - Sluhan, Clyde, 1996 and undated (Folder 23: 10)
  - Smaby, W. A., 1970 (Folder 23: 11)
  - Smith, Alice, 1967 (Folder 23: 12)
  - Smith, Allan F., 1978 (Folder 23: 13)
  - Smith, Anne L., 1987 (Folder 23: 14)
  - Smith, Brenton H., 1970-1971 (Folder 23: 15)
  - Smith, Bryan F., 1976-1978 (Folder 23: 16)
  - Smith, D. A., 1985 (Folder 23: 17)
  - Smith, G. Kerry, 1970 (Folder 23: 18)
  - Smith, Lacey Baldwin, 1986 (Folder 23: 19)
  - Smith, Mary S., 1989 (Folder 23: 20)
  - Smith, Mortimer, 1970-1971 (Folder 23: 21)
  - Smith, Richard W., 1968 (Folder 23: 22)
  - Smyd, Edwin S., 1970 (Folder 23: 23)
  - Smythe, Ormond, 1988 (Folder 23: 24)
  - Snare, Francis, 1969 (Folder 23: 25)
  - Solari, Rafael A., 1968-1973 (Folder 23: 26)
  - Solchanyk, Roman, 1974 (Folder 23: 27)
  - Soloway, Richard A., 1985 (Folder 23: 28)
  - Sommerfeldt, John R., 1966-1986 (Folder 23: 29)
  - Sonderegger, Richard, 1967-1970 (Folder 23: 30)
  - Sowell, Thomas, 1975-1976 (Folder 23: 31)
  - Spann, John R., 1986 (Folder 23: 32)
  - Spence, Clark, 1970 (Folder 23: 33)
  - Spirey, Allen, 1971 and undated (Folder 23: 34)
  - Spivack, John M., 1986 (Folder 23: 35)
  - Spivey, W. Allen, undated (Folder 23: 36)
  - Spurr, Stephen H., 1966-1971 (Folder 23: 37)
  - Stanford University, 1970-1980 (Folder 23: 38)
  - Stanlis, Peter J., 1965-1966 (Folder 23: 39)
  - Stannard, Richard, undated (Folder 23: 40)
  - Starbuck, Dane, 1992 (Folder 23: 41)
  - Stark, Gary D., 1983-1984 (Folder 23: 42)
  - Starr, Chester G., 1981 (Folder 23: 43)
  - Stave, Bruce M., 1986 (Folder 23: 44)
  - Stearns, Peter N., 1967-1986 (Folder 23: 45)
  - Steeples, Douglas W., 1971 (Folder 23: 46)
  - Stehlin, Stewart, 1986 (Folder 23: 47)
  - Stein, Ronald H., 1985-1996 (Folder 23: 48)
  - Steiner, Bruce E., 1971 (Folder 23: 49)
  - Steinhoff, William, 1969-1987 and undated (Folder 23: 50)
  - Sterk, Lois, 1970 (Folder 23: 51)
  - Sterling, Robert, 1970 (Folder 23: 52)
  - Stern, Mark Otto, 1993 and undated (Folder 23: 53)
  - Steudtner, Fritz, 1972 (Folder 23: 54)
  - Stigler, George J., 1971 (Folder 23: 55)
  - Stoddard, Harriet, 1979-1981 (Folder 23: 56)
  - Stolz, Benjamine A., 1986-1987 (Folder 23: 57)
  - Stone, Lawrence M., 1983 (Folder 23: 58)
  - Sue, Wallace, 1971 (Folder 23: 59)
  - Sullivan, Anthony T. (Box 24)
    - 1970-1974 and undated (Folder 24: 1)
    - 1975-1984 (Folder 24: 2)
    - 1985-1989 (Folder 24: 3)
    - 1990-1997 (Folder 24: 4)
  - Sullivan, Richard E., 1967-1969 (Folder 24: 5)
  - Sullivan, Richard H., 1969 (Folder 24: 6)
  - Sullivan, Sandra L., 1989 and undated (Folder 24: 7)
  - Super, Bob, 1984 (Folder 24: 8)
  - Sussman, Alfred S., 1970 (Folder 24: 9)
  - Swab, W. H., 1970 (Folder 24: 10)
  - Swarthmore College, 1970 (Folder 24: 11)
  - Synon, John J., 1968 (Folder 24: 12)
  - Szaz, Z. Michael, 1970 (Folder 24: 13)
  - Szporluk, Roman, 1982 (Folder 24: 14)
  - Tafel, Herman, 1977 (Folder 24: 15)
  - Talbott, David N., 1970 (Folder 24: 16)
  - Tanaskovic, Nicholas J., 1969 (Folder 24: 17)
  - Taylor, James B., 1986 (Folder 24: 18)
  - Taylor, John H., 1971 (Folder 24: 19)
  - Taylor, Robert M., 1964 (Folder 24: 20)
  - Teague, Randal Cornell, 1969-1970 (Folder 24: 21)
  - Templeton, Kenneth S., Jr., 1965-1973 (Folder 24: 22)
  - Tentler, Thomas N., 1984-1985 (Folder 24: 23)
  - Terrill, Dean, 1965 (Folder 24: 24)
  - Theodorson, George A., 1970 (Folder 24: 25)
  - Theroux, David J., 1993 (Folder 24: 26)
  - Thimme, Annelise
    - Undated (Folder 24: 27)
    - 1977-1978 (Folder 24: 28)
    - 1979-1980 (Box-folder 25: 1)
    - 1981-1984 (Folder 25: 2)
    - 1985-1991 (Folder 25: 3)
  - Thomas, Mark R., 1986 (Folder 25: 4)
  - Thomas, S. Bernard, 1983 (Folder 25: 5)
  - Thompson, L. V., 1983 (Folder 25: 6)
  - Thompson, Mack, 1975 (Folder 25: 7)
  - Thorne, Ms., 1984 (Folder 25: 8)
  - Thornton, J. Mills, 1980 (Folder 25: 9)
  - Thorpe, James III, 1981 (Folder 25: 10)
  - Thorson, Thomas L., 1972 (Folder 25: 11)
  - Thorwaldsen, Roland, 1986 (Folder 25: 12)
  - Thrupp, Sylvia L., 1957 (Folder 25: 13)
  - Thum, Richard L. Mrs., 1970 (Folder 25: 14)
  - Thurston, Robet W., 1979 (Folder 25: 15)
  - Tiffany, David H., 1968 (Folder 25: 16)
  - Tilly, Louise A., 1981-1984 (Folder 25: 17)
  - Tilton, George R.
    - Undated (Folder 25: 18-20)
    - 1970-1980 (Box-folder 26: 1)
    - 1981-1983 (Folder 26: 2)
    - 1984 (Folder 26: 3)
    - 1985 (Folder 26: 4)
    - 1986 (Folder 26: 5)
    - 1987-1988 (Folder 26: 6)
    - 1989-1991 (Folder 26: 7)
  - Times Sunday Magazine, 1969 (Box-folder 27: 1)
  - Todorovich, Miro M., 1971-1987 (Folder 27: 2)
  - Tompson, Richard S., 1966 (Folder 27: 3)
  - Tonsor, Charles A., Jr., 1971-1976 (Folder 27: 4)
  - Tonsor, Maxine and Ed, undated (Folder 27: 5)
  - Tonsor, Steve and Sue, 1978-1990 (Folder 27: 6)
  - Trammell, Georgiann, 1974 (Folder 27: 7)
  - Trapp, Walter B., 1969 (Folder 27: 8)
  - Trautmann, Thomas R., 1984 (Folder 27: 9)
  - Trisco, Robert, 1966-1993. (Folder 27: 10)
    See also Catholic Historical Review and American Catholic Historical Association
  - Trosco, James E., 1974 (Folder 27: 11)
  - Trowbridge, Keith W., 1970-1981 (Folder 27: 12)
  - Trowbridge, Ronald L., undated (Folder 27: 13)
  - Troxler, Carole, 1988 (Folder 27: 14)
  - Trubman, Howard, 1969 (Folder 27: 15)
  - Tucker, Herbert F., 1984 (Folder 27: 16)
  - Tulkki, Mark R., 1991 (Folder 27: 17)
  - Turner, Arlin, 1961 (Folder 27: 18)
  - Turyn, Alexander, Mrs., 1977 (Folder 27: 19)
  - Tuskegee Institute, 1970 (Folder 27: 20)
  - Tyrmand, Leopold, 1984 (Folder 27: 21)
  - Tyrrell, R. Emmett, Jr., 1969-1974 (Folder 27: 22)
  - Underbrink, Robert, 1971 (Folder 27: 23)
  - Unfug, Douglas A., 1970-1985 (Folder 27: 24)
  - University of Alberta, 1984 (Folder 27: 25)
  - University of California at Los Angeles, 1982 (Folder 27: 26)
  - University of San Francisco, 1977-1979 (Folder 27: 27)
  - University of Texas at Dallas, 1978-1988 (Folder 27: 28)
  - University of Toledo, 1982 (Folder 27: 29)
  - Uyl, Douglas Den, 1989-1997 (Folder 27: 30)
  - Valis, Wayne H., 1968-1971 (Folder 27: 31)
  - Van Engen, John, 1985 (Folder 27: 32)
  - Vann, James Allen, 1975-1985 (Folder 27: 33)
  - Vann, Richard T., undated (Folder 27: 34)
  - Varga, Nicholas, 1989 (Folder 27: 35)
  - Veerkamp, Pat, 1984 (Folder 27: 36)
  - Vella, John M., 1994-1996 (Folder 27: 37)
  - Venter, Casper S. C., 1979-1980 (Folder 27: 38)
  - Vermillion, W. H., Jr., 1971 (Folder 27: 39)
  - Victorian Studies, 1959-1971 and undated (Folder 27: 40)
  - Viditch, Joseph J., 1968 (Folder 27: 41)
  - Vieson, Paul, 1986 (Folder 27: 42)
  - Vigilante, Richard, 1986 (Folder 27: 43)
  - Vinovskis, Maris A., 1986 (Folder 27: 44)
  - Vinson, Fred M., Jr., 1967 (Folder 27: 45)
  - Vinyard, JoEllen, 1985 (Folder 27: 46)
  - Vital Speeches of the Day, 1970 (Folder 27: 47)
  - Vitzthum, Richard C., 1970 (Folder 27: 48)
  - Vivas, Eliseo, 1968-1979 and undated (Folder 27: 49)
  - Voegelin, Eric, 1966-1969. (Folder 27: 50)
  - Volis, Wayne H., 1971 (Folder 27: 51)
  - Vondung, Klaus, 1978-1979 (Folder 27: 52)
  - Voss, Earl H., 1972-1975 (Folder 27: 53)
  - Vree, Dale, 1975-1979 (Folder 27: 54)
  - Wagner, George, 1983-1984 (Folder 27: 55)
  - Wagner, John, 1983-1996 (Box-folder 28: 1)
  - Wakai, Ted, 1970 (Folder 28: 2)
  - Waldman, Marilyn, 1986 (Folder 28: 3)
  - Walker, Donna Wessel, 1984 (Folder 28: 4)
  - Walker, Franklin A., 1969 (Folder 28: 5)
  - Walker, Graham H., 1986 (Folder 28: 6)
  - Wall, Annalee, 1970 (Folder 28: 7)
  - Wall, Irwin M., 1986 (Folder 28: 8)
  - Wallace, W. Allen, 1970 (Folder 28: 9)
  - Waller, George M., 1983 (Folder 28: 10)
  - Wallerstein, Immanuel, 1970 (Folder 28: 11)
  - Wall Street Journal, 1969-1981 (Folder 28: 12)
  - Wallis, W. Allen, 1969-1970 (Folder 28: 13)
  - Walter, Scott, 1993 (Folder 28: 14)
  - Wandel, Winnie(?), 1986 (Folder 28: 15)
  - Ward, Charlotte, 1968 (Folder 28: 16)
  - Ward, James E., 1971 (Folder 28: 17)
  - Ward, Leo R., 1971-1972 (Folder 28: 18)
  - Ware, Beverly(?), circa 1980 (Folder 28: 19)
  - Ware, Richard A.
    - Undated (Folder 28: 20)
    - 1963-1968 (Folder 28: 21)
    - 1969-1971 (Folder 28: 22)
    - 1972-1974 (Folder 28: 23)
    - 1975-1976 (Folder 28: 24)
    - 1977-1979 (Folder 28: 25)
    - 1980-1996 (Folder 28: 26)
  - Warner, Robert M., 1970-1971 (Folder 28: 27)
  - Warwick, James Noel, undated (Folder 28: 28)
  - Washington Times, 1986-1987 (Folder 28: 29)
  - Watson, J. H. Adam, 1984 (Folder 28: 30)
  - Wattles, G. M., 1970 (Folder 28: 31)
  - Watts, G. R., 1968 (Folder 28: 32)
  - Watts, W. A., 1969 (Folder 28: 33)
  - Weatherford, Willis D., 1973 (Box-folder 29: 1)
  - Weaver, Mary Jo, 1973-1982 (Folder 29: 2)
  - Webb, Joe, undated (Folder 29: 3)
  - Webber, Howard R., 1978 (Folder 29: 4)
  - Weber, Edward, 1984 (Folder 29: 5)
  - Wedemeyer, George E., 1968 (Folder 29: 6)
  - Weden, Elmer A., Jr., 1971 (Folder 29: 7)
  - Weeks, Stephen C., 1986 (Folder 29: 8)
  - Weinberg, Gerhard L., 1967-1972 (Folder 29: 9)
  - Weir, Charles Robert, Mrs., 1970 (Folder 29: 10)
  - Weiss, James, 1987-1988 (Folder 29: 11)
  - Weiss, John, 1970 (Folder 29: 12)
  - Werlein, Leila, undated (Folder 29: 13)
  - Wesner, David O., 1981 (Folder 29: 14)
  - Wessman, Rosemary, 1969 (Folder 29: 15)
  - West, Elliott, 1986 (Folder 29: 16)
  - West, Kenneth B., 1968 (Folder 29: 17)
  - Wester(?), Roger, undated (Folder 29: 18)
  - Wharton, W. W., 1970 (Folder 29: 19)
  - Wheaton, Bernice, 1987 (Folder 29: 20)
  - Wheeler, Benjamin W., 1972 (Folder 29: 21)
  - Wheeler, Richard S., 1974 (Folder 29: 22)
  - White House, 1970-1982 (Folder 29: 23)
  - White, Janice L., 1976 (Folder 29: 24)
  - White, Kathleen, 1975 (Folder 29: 25)
  - White, Lyn M., 1992 (Folder 29: 26)
  - White, Timothy O., 1983 (Folder 29: 27)
  - Whitney, Gleaves, 1988-1992 (Folder 29: 28)
  - Wick, Charles Z., 1982 (Folder 29: 29)
  - Wickre, Bill, undated (Folder 29: 30)
  - Wiener, Philip P., 1967 (Folder 29: 31)
  - Wiggins, James W., 1968-1970 (Folder 29: 32)
  - Wilke, Ekkehard-Teja, 1971 (Folder 29: 33)
  - Will, George F., undated (Folder 29: 34)
  - Willard, Andrew, 1978 (Folder 29: 35)
  - Willcox(?), 1966-1967 (Folder 29: 36)
  - Willcox, Christopher, undated (Folder 29: 37)
  - Willcox, W. B., 1968 (Folder 29: 38)
  - Williams, Donald E., undated (Folder 29: 39)
  - Williamson, W. Rulon, 1970 (Folder 29: 40)
  - Willson, John, 1987 (Folder 29: 41)
  - Wilson, Francis G., 1965 (Folder 29: 42)
  - Windham, William T., 1985 (Folder 29: 43)
  - Winnie, Laurence H., 1984 and undates (Folder 29: 44)
  - Winsor, Philip, 1986 (Folder 29: 45)
  - Winstead, Elizabeth, 1987 (Folder 29: 46)
  - Witonski, Peter P., 1968-1970 (Folder 29: 47)
  - WKBD TV, 1969 (Folder 29: 48)
  - Woehrer, Patricia, 1986 (Folder 29: 49)
  - Wolf, Hans, 1973 (Folder 29: 50)
  - Wolfe, Bertram D., 1975-1976. (Folder 29: 51)
  - Wolfe, Gregory, 1981-1994 (Folder 29: 52)
  - Womack, John, Jr., 1984 (Folder 29: 53)
  - Women's Republican Club, 1971 and undated (Folder 29: 54)
  - Wood, Gordon S., 1975 (Folder 29: 55)
  - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars, 1972 (Folder 29: 56)
  - Woodruff, Douglas, 1959 (Folder 29: 57)
  - Woodstock, Betty, 1970 (Folder 29: 58)
  - Woodward C. Vann, 1980 (Folder 29: 59)
  - Woody, Stella, undated (Folder 29: 60)
  - Wormold, F. L., 1970 (Folder 29: 61)
  - Wortman, Roy, 1982 (Folder 29: 62)
  - Wright, Susan, 1967 (Folder 29: 63)
  - Wu, Yuan-li, 1969 (Folder 29: 64)
  - Wynn, Charles B., 1969 (Folder 29: 65)
  - Yale University, 1976 (Folder 29: 66)
  - Yates, Anne C., 1970 (Folder 29: 67)
  - Yiotis, Gayle, 1984 (Folder 29: 68)
  - Young Americans for Freedom, Inc., 1980 (Folder 29: 69)
  - Young, Francis A., 1964 (Folder 29: 70)
  - Young, M. Norvel, 1970 (Folder 29: 71)
  - Young, Theodore A., 1986 (Folder 29: 72)
  - Zeltman, Yadja, 1970 (Folder 29: 73)
  - Zesmer, David, 1984 (Folder 29: 74)
  - Zilly, G. Sam, Mrs., 1970-1971 (Folder 29: 75)
  - Zimmerman, Paul A., 1969 (Folder 29: 76)
  - Zoeller, Michael, 1994 (Folder 29: 77)
- Speeches and Writings, 1958-1999 and undated. (Box 30)
  Articles, book reviews, lists of conferences and seminars, responses to his speeches, notes, outlines, poems, and remarks, arranged chronologically
  - General
    - Untitled holograph and typescript loose pages about social idealism, East-West conflict, and higher education, undated, and agreement with the publishers, Rhinehart & Company Incorporated, 1958 (Folder 30: 1)
    - Records of participations, 1981-1996
      - Contemporary Religious Movements in Central Europe, undated (Folder 30: 2)
      - "Conservatism and Libertarianism: Prospects and Problems of Theoretical Reconciliation and 'Fusion,'" 1981; Seminar on "Augustine's City of God,", 1986 January 16-18. (Folder 30: 3)
        Includes printed copies of articles
      - Seminar on "Human Nature, Christianity and Liberty," Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1996 January 26-28 (Folder 30: 4)
    - Records of response to speeches
      - 1968 June  1969 May (Folder 30: 5)
      - 1969 June  1982 April (Folder 30: 6)
    - Records of speaking engagements
      - Undated (Folder 30: 7)
      - 1967-1977 (Folder 30: 8)
  - "Absolutism and Equality,", undated. (Folder 30: 9)
    Holograph and typescript
  - "The Age of the Hellenistic Monarchies,", undated. (Folder 30: 10)
    Holograph. Includes printed matter
  - "Albert Schweitzer and the Crisis of Protestant Liberalism (1875-1965),", undated. (Folder 30: 11)
    Holograph
  - "The American Catholic and Political Order,", undated. (Folder 30: 12)
    Typescript
  - "The American Conservative,", undated. (Folder 30: 13)
    Holograph outline
  - "Arcadia,", undated. (Folder 30: 14)
    Holograph and typescript. Includes related correspondence
  - "Arcadia and Childhood," and "Camelot, Arcadia and the Myth of Regeneration,", undated. (Folder 30: 15)
    Holograph. Includes related materials
  - "Aristotle and Equality,", undated. (Folder 30: 16)
    Holograph. Includes a letter from Robert Trisco, 1968 June 18
  - "Armenian Catholic and Political Order,", undated. (Folder 30: 17)
    Holograph. Includes holograph fragment and photocopy of a typescript bibliography
  - Articles
    - About Bismarck, undated. (Folder 30: 18)
    - About Brooks Adams, undated. (Folder 30: 19)
    - About David Herbert Lawrence (1885-1950), undated. (Folder 30: 20)
    - About Egypt, undated. (Folder 30: 21)
    - About German Historical Thought in the Eighteenth Century, undated. (Folder 30: 22)
    - About Justus Möser, 1720-1794, undated. (Folder 30: 23)
    - About old catholic church, undated. (Folder 30: 24)
      Holograph and galley. Includes printed matter
    - About a special number of Modern Age devoted to the Future or Non-Future of Socialism, undated. (Folder 30: 25)
  - "Athena's Bat,", undated. (Folder 30: 26)
  - "The Avant Garde,", undated. (Folder 30: 27)
    Holograph. Includes related printed materials and photocopy of a printed bibliography
  - "Bigotry, Diversity, and Standards," speech, undated. (Folder 30: 28)
  - Biographical sketch of Henry Regnery, undated. (Folder 30: 29)
    Holograph and typescript. Includes printed copy of an article by Alfred S. Regnery, 1985 Fall
  - "The Bishops and the Bomb," speech, undated. (Folder 30: 30)
  - "Bunny Hugging Is so Bourgeois,", undated. (Box-folder 31: 1)
  - "Burckhardt at Home,", undated. (Folder 31: 2)
  - "Camelot, Arcadia and the Myth of Regeneration,", undated. (Folder 31: 3)
    Typescript and holograph notes. Includes related materials
  - "Card-Board Imitation Leather,", undated. (Folder 31: 4)
  - "The Career of Adolf Hitler: Stupidity as a Popular Movement," review of Ian Kershaw, Hitler 1889-1936, undated. (Folder 31: 5)
  - "The Case of Gary Wills,", undated. (Folder 31: 6)
  - "The Case for Prejudices,", undated. (Folder 31: 7)
    Holograph. Includes typescript notes
  - "The Catholic Revival, 1815-1870,", undated. (Folder 31: 8)
    Holograph outline and notes
  - "The City and Literature,", undated. (Folder 31: 9)
    Holograph and typescript. Includes related printed matter
  - "The Cliff Dwellers after Eighty Years,", undated. (Folder 31: 10)
  - "The Cold War,", undated. (Folder 31: 11)
  - "Conservatism and History,", undated. (Folder 31: 12)
  - "The Conservative Element in American Liberalism," proposed lecture, undated. (Folder 31: 13)
    Typescript. Includes related materials
  - "The Conservative Search for Identity,", undated. (Folder 31: 14)
  - "Conservative and the Totalitarian Enlightenment: Equality in the Age of Reason,", undated. (Folder 31: 15)
  - "Conservatives as a Creative Minority in a time of Cultural Crisis,", undated. (Folder 31: 16)
  - "The Contrived Corridor," review of John Lukacs, Historical Consciousness: The Remembered Past, undated. (Folder 31: 17)
  - "The Counter-Cultures vs. American Business,", undated. (Folder 31: 18)
  - "The Counter Enlightenment,", undated. (Folder 31: 19)
  - "Cracks in the Kremlin Wall,", undated. (Folder 31: 20)